businessoffashion.com 2014-06-30

# Privacy Policy - BoF - The Business of Fashion

Last Updated June 26, 2013

**GENERAL RULES AND DEFINITIONS**

This page describes the Privacy Policy that govern your use of certain Business of Fashion digital products, including the website www.businessoffashion.com and mobile applications, offered by [The Business of Fashion](http://www.businessoffashion.com/the-business-of-fashion) Ltd. (“BoF”, “us” or “we”).

If you choose to use [www.businessoffashion.com](http://www.businessoffashion.com/), any mobile sites and applications, or any of the features of this site (the “Site”), including but not limited to RSS, API, software and other downloads (collectively, the “Services”), you will be agreeing to abide by all of the terms and conditions of the BoF Privacy Policy.  Your continued use of the Site and Services now, or following the posting of notice of changes in these operating rules, will indicate acceptance by you of such rules.

It is your responsibility to read and understand this privacy policy. **If you do not agree to all of this privacy policy and do not wish to be bound by it, you are not authorised to access or otherwise use the Site or Services.**   In reviewing this privacy policy, please also read our [Terms & Conditions](http://businessoffashion.com/tcs)

We may change, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time, which shall become effective immediately upon posting. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy prior to each use of the Site and Services and by continuing to use this Site and Services, you agree to any changes.  

We are committed to safeguarding your privacy online.  We appreciate that you do not want any personal information you provide to us distributed indiscriminately and here we explain how we collect information, what we do with it and what controls you have. This privacy policy may change from time to time.

This privacy policy explains the following:

1.    What personal information we collect about you;

2.    How we store your personal information;

3.    How your personal information is used;

4.    Whether we will disclose your personal information to anyone else;

5.    Any age restrictions on supplying personal information to us;

6.    How long may we may keep your personal information;

7.    Our use of cookies and web beacons on the Websites and your right to be informed about and consent to these cookies; and

8.    How to contact us.

### Personal Information we collect about you

1.1 We collect personally identifiable information about you (your “Data”) through the use of enquiry and registration forms and the provision of your details to us either online or offline.  The elements of your Data that we collect may include:

  * Name
  * Job title
  * Company name
  * Company address, phone and fax number
  * Home address and phone number
  * Mobile telephone number
  * E-mail address
  * Payment details such as credit card information
  * Date of birth
  * Educational history, work experience and other information from your CV if you provide this to us
  * Market research data such as readership patterns
  * Usage statistics
  * We may also collect information that we request from you regarding your use of our service or that we collect automatically about your visit to our sites.

1.3 There are links on the Websites to third party websites over which BoF has no control. BoF accepts no responsibility or liability for any third party practices on third party websites. BoF advises you to carefully read third party privacy statements prior to the use of any third party website.

### Storage of Personal Information

2.1 The Websites have appropriate technical and organisational measures in place to protect against unauthorised or unlawful use of your personal information as well as the accidental loss, destruction or damage of your personal information whilst under our control. However no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and whilst we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

2.2 Due to the international nature of the internet, the collecting and processing of your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy will often involve transferring such information between countries in which BoF, other companies in the BoF group of companies and strategic partners are located.

2.3 BoF shall take steps to ensure that any transfer of your personal information to a country or territory outside the European Economic Area, whose laws provide for a lesser standard of protection for your personal information than that provided under European law, shall be made subject to arrangements which will require that your personal information be processed to a standard compliant with European data protection laws.

### Use of Personal Information

3.1  We use your Data for purposes which may include:

  * providing our users with a personalised service
  * processing orders, registrations and enquiries
  * conducting market research surveys
  * allowing users to participate in interactive features of our service, where they choose to do so
  * providing reports to our Clients containing information about usage under corporate licenses
  * running competitions, prize draws and promotions
  * providing you with information about products and services we offer
  * sharing your Data with third party organisations who offer products or services which we feel may be of interest to you
  * contacting you about specific recruitment opportunities if you register search criteria information on our recruitment sites.
  * monitoring compliance with our Terms and Conditions and Copyright Policy
  * providing you with information about The Business of Fashion or our business partners’ products and services
  * send out email alerts

3.2  We may also disclose your information to business partners and to third party suppliers we engage to provide services which involve processing data on our behalf, successors in title to our business or in accordance with a properly executed court order or as otherwise required to do so by law.

3.3   We reserve the right to fully co-operate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requiring or requesting us to disclose the identity or other usage details of any user of our sites.

3.4  We also use information in aggregate form (so that no individual user is identified by name):

  * to build up marketing profiles
  * to aid strategic development
  * to manage our relationship with advertisers
  * to audit usage of the site.

3.5  We may use technology on the registration page of our website, which may record user movements, including page scrolling, mouse clicks and text entered. The data we collect in this way helps us to identify usability issues, to improve the assistance and technical support we can provide to users and is also used for aggregated and statistical reporting purposes.

3.6   BoF may also contact you about your registration details even if you have opted-out of or declined to consent to receiving promotional emails.

Transfer of Data:

3.7  User Data may be transferred outside BoF to data processors such as fulfilment houses but they will act only on our instructions to provide the services required.

3.8  The Internet is a global environment. Using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing the BoF site and communicating electronically with us you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way. By agreeing to our transfer of your Data to third party organisations for them to send you details of products and services offered (as detailed above) you are deemed to provide your consent to any transfer of your Data to organisations based outside the European Economic Area.

### Disclosures

4.1 We may disclose your personal information to partners of BoF who supply services to you on behalf of BoF and who need to process personal information in the provision of such services.  When you request goods and services from BoF, you are consenting to the disclosure of your personal information to BoF’s partners who may provide such goods and services.  BoF will not disclose any of your personal information to any other third parties without your express consent.

4.2 We may disclose depersonalised data (such as aggregated statistics) about the users of our Websites in order to describe our sales, customers, traffic patterns and other site information to prospective partners, advertisers, investors and other reputable third parties and for other lawful purposes, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.

4.3 Under certain circumstances we may occasionally be required by law, court order or governmental authority to disclose certain types of personal information and we reserve the right to comply with any such legally binding request.  Examples of the type of situation where this would occur would be:

  * in the administration of justice
  * where we have to defend ourselves legally
  * in complying with the mandatory requirements of a government department collecting information on employee benefits.

### Age Restrictions

5.1  If you are aged 16 or under, please get your parent/guardian’s permission beforehand whenever you provide personal information to the Websites. Users without this consent are not allowed to provide us with personal information. If we become aware that you are under [16] and are attempting to or have submitted personal information via the Websites without your parent/guardian’s permission, we will not accept such information and we will take steps to remove such information from our records. This may involve us having to access and verify your age and other relevant details.

### How long will we keep your Personal Information

6.1 We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as is necessary to provide you with the goods and/or services you have requested.

### Use of Cookies

7.1  We may collect information about your computer including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type for system administration as part of our audit trail process.  ”Cookies” are pieces of information that a website transfers to your hard drive to store and sometimes track information about you. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can change your browser to prevent that. You are not obliged to accept cookies and you can adjust your browser’s setting to prevent it from accepting cookies on your computer – go to [www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/) for instructions on how to disable cookies.  However, you may not be able to take full advantage of our Websites if you do so. Cookies are specific to the server that created them and cannot be accessed by other servers, which means they cannot be used to track your movements around the web. Although they can be used to store information which may identify a user’s computer, cookies do not personally identify users and passwords and credit card information are not stored in cookies.

7.2 The following cookies are set automatically when you visit The Business of Fashion website:

Third Party Cookies

**Domain: businessoffashion.com  **

Cookies: __utma, __utmb, __utmc, __utmz by Google

The Business of Fashion uses Google Analytics, which sets a cookie in order to anonymously identify when users return to specific websites.

Google uses the information sent with this cookie to store a history of website pages visited in a user’s session. This data will not be used to associate any part of your identity, anonymous or not, with any other data held by Google.

Further information about how to opt-out of this cookie can be found at <http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacypolicy.html>

**Domain: facebook.com**

Cookies: Facebook Like Button cookies

When you create or log in to an account on [http://www.facebook.com](http://www.facebook.com/) cookies are stored on your computer in order to remain logged-in to your facebook account when visiting [http://www.facebook.com](http://www.facebook.com/)again. The Facebook Like Button used on our website is hosted by Facebook and your browser therefore sends this cookie data to Facebook when creating the button inside your browser. This data is used by Facebook in order to associate the Facebook Like Button with your Facebook account. This information is not accessible to us, and is not sent to us by Facebook.

More information about this cookie and Facebook’s Privacy Policy can be found at <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/your-info-on-other#socialplugin>

**Domain: twitter.com**

Cookies: Twitter Share Button

When you create or log in to an account on [http://www.twitter.com](http://www.twitter.com/)  cookies are stored on your computer in order to remain logged-in to your twitter account when visiting [http://www.twitter.com](http://www.twitter.com/) again. The Twitter Share Button used on our website is hosted by [http://www.twitter.com](http://www.twitter.com/)and your browser therefore sends this cookie data to Twitter when creating the button inside your browser. This data is used by Twitter in order to associate the Twitter Share Button with your Twitter account. This data is not accessible to us, and is not sent to us by Twitter.

More information about this cookie and Twitter’s Privacy Policy can be found at <https://twitter.com/privacy>

**Domain: google.com**

Cookies: Google +1 Button

When you create or log in to an account on [http://www.google.com](http://www.twitter.com/)  cookies are stored on your computer in order to remain logged-in to your Google account when visiting [http://www.google.com](http://www.google.com/) again. The Google +1 Button used on our website is hosted by [http://www.google.com](http://www.google.com/)and your browser therefore sends this cookie data to Google when creating the button inside your browser. This data is used by Google in order to associate the Google +1 Button with your Google account. This data is not accessible to us, and is not sent to us by Google.

**Domain: ad.uk.doubleclick.net**

Cookies: ad.uk.doubleclick.net

BoF uses Google to serve advertisements. Advertisements are received from Google servers to your browser along with a cookie to anonymously identify you as you visit websites which serve advertising from Google servers.

More information about this cookie, including how to opt-out of receiving the cookie can be found at <http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/>

**Domain: Any**

Cookies: Advertisement cookie

From time to time, advertisers may include digital assets which set cookies on an advertiser’s domain or on the domain of a The Business of Fashion website. These cookies will only store anonymous information about your interaction with a specific advert and will not be used to personally identify you.

You may opt-out find out more information, including how to opt-out of these cookies being set in your browser by visiting <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices>

### Access to Personal Information

8.1 If you wish to access the personal information held by us, you should contact us using the information provided below.

8.2 We will provide you with copies of all the personal information we hold about you, on payment of a nominal administration charge of £10.

8.3 Please help us to keep our records of your personal information up-to-date by notifying us of any changes or corrections to the personal information we hold about you.

### Contact Details

9.1  If you do not understand or accept this privacy policy or wish to contact us concerning any matter relating to your personal information then please email [info@businessoffashion.com](mailto:info@businessoffashion.com).
